Hello, hello, welcome to a new latex video. I received new latex pieces by Illion Harness.
For example, this pink dress. Yes, it's pink and yes, it has a natural transparent inlay here.
It's going to be interesting.
But I also... Let's check this box out. Got this one.
well let me put the
that one away
have a look at that crazy box
and I'm not sure what it is
I think it's a wolf
first I thought it's a pink
but I think it's a wolf
anyway
underneath is the catsuit
and it's orange
so an orange bag zipper with black zip and I'm going to change into the first piece now
alright the dress and I have some color matching mittens arm warmers I mean what are these called
with no fingers or they are not gloss in German I would say Stulten but I don't know the exact
English term for that anyway um it's pink and I like the cute cut out here reminds me a bit
of a mustache the shape here gives a bit of an under boob peekaboo
I'm wearing size small I think it would fit a bit better with the smaller boobs like with a
b cup because I am having 75c here and I think yeah a bit smaller would be more comfortable
anyway um I'm normally not a fan of transparent natural latex I think this amount of natural
transparent is okay I quite like it here in this combination everything is a gauge of 0.4
millimeters and I think you have various color options so check out the Elin Harness shop
I'm going to take some pictures now and after that I will wear the catsuit but first let me
turn around for you again I think it's a cute combination with the color and a cute little
dress of course you will see the pictures on my Instagram as well if you are not following me
there check that one out and I'm going to change into the catsuit now catsuit and I used a lot of
silicone oil dressing aid to get into this one because it's also 0.4 millimeter gauge which
makes it not as stretchy as 0.25 millimeter so a bit more help and time is needed to get into that
one but what made the whole thing easier is the back zipper that runs along all of the back until
the crotch here so I could zip it, unzip it and then zip it up. I think that's the right way around
and yeah get into it better. And now I paired it with some black heels to balance out the black
zipper. We do have cups here. I think they fit great for a natural A-cup. I decided to wear a
push-up bra underneath because they wouldn't fit me anyway so I was like
more is more super push-up bra it is and I think it looks really well together
with the whole outfit it's orange I mean the color is really really bright I like
it more than yellow and otherwise it's orange I'm not used to seeing myself in
such a bright colored catsuit because normally my catsuits are black and
smoky black and teal and whatever or purple maybe but this is something new I
kind of feel like construction worker working on the streets and having to
wear a signal color but of course it kind of looks good because of blue hair blue
and orange go well together blue and everything goes well together I mean
what doesn't go well together with blue? Name one thing. Anyway, unique combination. I don't know if I would have chosen orange myself for like getting a new catsuit to wear all the time. I would prefer black for like my basic catsuit but changing things up is also nice.
I want to try something and add a corset and maybe some other stuff to create a phone look. Let's see. Okay I added a corset, a neck corset combination thingy. I don't know, collar.
which is attached to the corset via various straps and some fingerless gloves.
I'm going to take pictures with it in a second and I have to redo pictures with this corset and this chocolate beaker.
Someone deleted some photoshoot pictures I was supposed to get with this outfit here, with the corset.
anyway I think the combination of orange and black is really cool like with that amount of
black now put on top of the orange I even like the orange more before it was just so much orange
and now it looks like it was kind of an outfit created from the feet to the hands from head to
you know what I mean
also big thank you to Ilin Hannes for sending the catsuit and the dress to me
I have two more Ilin Hannes videos on my channel so you can check them out and
I'll post a photoshoot set on my patreon so join me there give a thumbs up and
subscribe to my channel leave a comment all that stuff thanks for your support
and I'll see you in the next video. Bye!